What's done in the dark will be brought to the light
Dominion is a documentary film directed by Chris Delforce.
Exposing the dark underbelly of modern animal agriculture through drones, hidden & handheld cameras, the
feature-length film explores the morality and validity of our dominion over the animal kingdom.
Narrator (voice), played by Rooney Mara.
Narrator (voice), played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Narrator (voice), played by Sia.
Narrator (voice), played by Sadie Sink.
Narrator (voice), played by Kat Von D.
Narrator (voice), played by Chris Delforce.
Dominion is a 2018 Australian documentary film filmed primarily with drones and hidden cameras inside Australian slaughterhouses and macro-farms with the aim
to expose an opaque and inhumane system, according to the film's writer, director, and producer, Chris Delforce, an animal rights activist.
The film documents multiple animal abuse industries in Australia, especially
agricultural livestock, while focusing its message on animal rights.
Dominion portrays the killing of animals through methods such as using carbon
dioxide to gas pigs, maceration of chicks, and skinning foxes alive.
The film explores themes of australia, zoo, exploitation, animals, animal abuse.
The tone is dark.